softzsolutions.com 2009-11-25

# Privacy Policy related to SEO Services provided by Softz Solutions, India

Home » Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy sets out how "Softz Solutions" uses and protects any information that you give "Softz Solutions" when you use this website.

"Softz Solutions" is committed to protecting your privacy. If, when using this website, you provide, or we collect, any information by which you can be identified, it will only be used in accordance with the guidelines outlined in this privacy policy.  
This policy is effective from October 1, 2008. 

"Softz Solutions" has the right to change this policy at any time so please check this document regularly if you are at all concerned about "Softz Solutions" and their handling of your personal information. 

**Personal information we may collect through the normal use of our website:**  

We may collect the following information: 

  * Name or job title 
  * Contact information including telephone number, fax number email address 
  * Location information such as zip / postal code 

**Where and why we gather information:**

The only reason "Softz Solutions" would purposely collect or view your data is via our website forms, for example our contact for on our contact page,or indirectly through website analytics. The following is what we do with this information:

  * Internal record keeping. 
  * Use the information to improve our services or products.
  * Although Softz Solutions does not send unsolicited mail, we may send an email to you if we feel you may be interested in a particular service or change in services.
  * Periodically, we may also contact you for market research purposes using the information you have provided such as, but not exclusive to: email, phone, fax or regular mail. 

**Your Security**  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have implemented and maintain suitable physical, managerial and procedural actions to ensure the safety and security of the information we collect online. 

**How Cookies can be Used**  
If your computer is set to accept Cookies, a cookie "file" will be placed on your hard drive when visiting a website. The Cookie then collects information as you use the website or the internet and uses the information it collects to tailor the web experience to you. An example of this may be the Cookie’s ability to "autocomplete" your name when typing it into a field on an internet form.

We use traffic log Cookies for statistical purposes only. By viewing traffic log Cookies, we can analyze web patterns on our website and improve our website thereby giving our visitor a better overall experience. Please be aware that cookies give us absolutely no personal information about you not do they give us any type of access whatsoever to your computer or any of its components or hardware. 

Most web browsers and applications automatically accept Cookies. You can turn Cookies off yourself, usually by entering the "Options" or "Security" area of your web browser or application. By turning Cookies off you may not get the full experience of the websites you visit.

**Outbound Links**  
Any links pointing from any of our pages to other websites or pages are there as points of interest. Once you click a link that takes you away from our page we are no longer responsible for your privacy or protection. This Privacy Policy is only binding while you are exclusively visiting our site. Although we use these outbound links to provide additional resources in good faith, we are not responsible for, nor do we necessarily agree, with the content you may find on those pages. 

**Outbound Links**  
Any links pointing from any of our pages to other websites or pages are there as points of interest. Once you click a link that takes you away from our page we are no longer responsible for your privacy or protection. This Privacy Policy is only binding while you are exclusively visiting our site. Although we use these outbound links to provide additional resources in good faith, we are not responsible for, nor do we necessarily agree, with the content you may find on those pages. 

**Collection of Information Options**  
You can stop the collection of your information by this website by not filling out any of the forms on this website's pages. If you have already filled out a form and do not want "Softz Solutions" to use your information for any reason including emails and promotions, you can simply email us at sandipkar[at]softzsolutions[dot]com. 

We will never sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.   
If any information we hold is incorrect or misrepresentative, please simply email us at the address above. 

The Privacy Policy above is for both your (the browser or customer) and our (Softz Solutions) protection. Softz Solutions will very rarely send promotional email to anyone, and occasionally sends information to their clients to which they already have a working relationship. Softz Solutions will never sell, lend, or make public your information to marketers, solicitors, or the like. Simply put, Softz Solutions does not want to send, nor receive, spam. 

Due to nature of our business we don't offer any refund or money back for any of our services. If you don't want to continue for our service, then just cancel your service by sending us a mail at contact[at]softzsolutions[dot]com and you won't be billed again. If you opt for one time service fee then also the payment is not refundable because once we'll deliver the product / service we don't have any control to get back it. Since it is digital product so we don't entertain any refund / money back request from our clients. Hope you'll understand it.

There is one exception of refund: If you sign up for a plan and if we feel that we can't do the project for you at that moment then we'll issue 100% refund within 7 working days. Refunds will be given at the discretion of the management.

By browsing our website you agree to comply with the following Terms and Conditions outlined in this document, which, in conjunction with our Privacy Policy, governs the relationship between you and Softz Solutions while you are viewing or using this website. 

**When using this website you are bound to these Terms of Use:**

  * Softz Solutions reserves the right to change any of the content on this website at any time. The content is there for your information and convenience should you chose to view it. 

  * We do not provide any guarantee as to the timeliness, accuracy, performance, suitability or completeness of the information offered or found on this site for any purpose. The user or viewer or "you" agree that such information may contain errors or inaccuracies and acknowledge that we expressly exclude liability for any such errors or inaccuracies to the fullest permissible extent of the law. 

  * The use of materials or information on this website is at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable. It is the viewer’s or user’s responsibility to ensure the products and services on this page herein meet your specific requirements or satisfaction. 

  * This information and material on this website is owned by and licensed to us. This material includes, but is not limited to, articles, copy, layout, design, look, graphics and appearances. Reproduction is strictly prohibited unless in adherence to the copyright notice, which is part of these terms and conditions. 

  * Softz Solutions acknowledges all trademarks used in this website that are not licensed to, or the property of, the website owner. 

  * Unauthorized use of this website may give to a claim for damages and be construed as a criminal offence. 

  * This site contains links to other websites. Read our Privacy Policy, which governs the relationship between you and Softz Solutions while you are viewing or using this website, for information on outbound links. We are not responsible for any damages, loss of information, collection of information or content on any website that is not our own, even if you, as the user, follow a link from our site to any other site in question. 

  * You must not create a link to this website, whether it is from another website, document, or other media, without Softz Solutions’ express prior written consent. 

  * The (your) use of this website and any dispute regarding this website or document is subject to the laws of India.
